Hello hello friends if you are a painter customer
and have properly installed Pradhan Mantri
Suraksha Bima Yojana and Pradhan Mantri Jeevan
Jyoti Bima Yojana in the bank
and you are checking which side of their account,
then in such a situation if you want to
download this certificate then
how can you download it if you
want to know then stay tuned in this video
we are going to talk on this topic only
Hello friends I am Pranav welcome to
Apply YouTube channel, for that
first we will
go to the bank account and show better percentage in the future
friends till now we have gone to Vatan
laptop test and here we have opened
Google, hmm let's start one work that is
download
MS Word,
so we have to
click on the subscribe button and hence we
click on the cloth by clicking on this link you will
get a new money, press it
I will put it in the description you
can directly click and come to the space,
so here first it is asking you to write your window phone
number, through this savings
bank account you have
applied for PM SBI and PM JS Vivah  I had done
Android and the same savings account
number will have to be entered here and I am also asking for an ad, so
after entering the bank's account number from here, you will have to enter your date of birth,
like cement, then
put it here for decades and click on the filter, now
we put both these things here and
click on the bottle
and here we have entered our account number and my account number
on the laptop, click on the fee button,
click on this button, here your
policy number and police number will be visible,
so you can see that your 12th number is the
last Amla and I have added your name, the
name is visible here and the police
number is shown here, you will have to click
on the bell button to download this policy, you will have to
click on this mill owners and you will get it within a day,
this fair goes away immediately, you get some time,
whatever we click on welcome, like we will
click on email, you are being
asked to enter the email ID here, if
you want to do it in this channel, then enter the same
email here, we will also send the email here  Let's
write the email address,
after entering the sample cloth here we will click on it, if we
click on the chain button then
within 58 days you will get eight wickets,
now you can check it with your email
and we have received it within half an hour
and if we check it here, a
little below you can see the download button, it will be
visible in Quetta, you can click it
and we have set our end in stock
and if you want to open it and see, we have this mail
in PDF format
and we can open it and see it
and here you can see this
policy which is visible in front of you, you can take a
print out and keep it with you, there is
capacity increase but friends,
before this I would like to tell you once that if
you download this by roti bore, the police
will joint your money in Izrat,
you can download it only within 30 days from Tuesday
and otherwise you will get a
message in your mobile, you
can download Kitna Devta Ki Jai, you can download it at the same time, then
you will
not be able to talk about it, in the
same way you can open ICICI Bank  What happened was
that the PM became SP and the PM came JDU, through
which you can download their flip, I
hope friends you liked this video, you must have come to
know about how you can download that tapped PM Maze Side Effect in IS back,
if you liked this video
please like the video and do not forget to subscribe to the channel, we will
meet again in the next video, one
with a pic, till then do the other one.